Guide to the Dial/Scofield Thayer Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Restricted Fragile, 4.8; (12 boxes)
  - Box 44, folder 1250 (Box 92, Folder 2725)
  - Box 44, folder 1251 (Box 92, Folder 2726)
  - Box 44, folder 1252 (Box 92, Folder 2727)
  - Box 44, folder 1253 (Box 92, Folder 2728)
  - Box 44, folder 1254 (Box 92, Folder 2729)
  - Box 44, folder 1257 (Box 92, Folder 2730)
  - Box 44, folder 1259 (Box 92, Folder 2731)
  - Box 44, folder 1260 (Box 92, Folder 2732)
  - Box 44, folder 1263 (Box 92, Folder 2733)
  - Box 44, folder 1264 (Box 92, Folder 2734)
  - Box 44, folder 1265 (Box 92, Folder 2735)
  - Box 44, folder 1266 (Box 92, Folder 2736)
  - Box 44, folder 1267 (Box 92, Folder 2737)
  - Box 44, folder 1268 (Box 92, Folder 2738)
  - Box 45, folder 1276 (Box 92, Folder 2739)
  - Box 45, folder 1277 (Box 92, Folder 2740)
  - Box 45, folder 1278 (Box 92, Folder 2741)
  - Box 45, folder 1279 (Box 92, Folder 2742)
  - Box 45, folder 1280 (Box 92, Folder 2743)
  - Box 45, folder 1281 (Box 92, Folder 2744)
  - Box 45, folder 1283 (Box 92, Folder 2745)
  - Box 45, folder 1284 (Box 92, Folder 2746)
  - Box 45, folder 1285 (Box 92, Folder 2747)
  - Box 45, folder 1294 (Box 92, Folder 2748)
  - Box 45, folder 1296 (Box 92, Folder 2749)
  - Box 46, folder 1307 (Box 92, Folder 2750)
  - Box 46, folder 1309 (Box 92, Folder 2751)
  - Box 46, folder 1313 (Box 92, Folder 2752)
  - Box 46, folder 1316 (Box 92, Folder 2753)
  - Box 46, folder 1317 (Box 92, Folder 2754)
  - Box 47, folder 1321 (Box 92, Folder 2755)
  - Box 47, folder 1322 (Box 92, Folder 2756)
  - Box 47, folder 1325 (Box 92, Folder 2757)
  - Box 47, folder 1327 (Box 92, Folder 2758)
  - Box 47, folder 1328 (Box 92, Folder 2759)
  - Box 47, folder 1331 (Box 92, Folder 2760)
  - Box 47, folder 1333 (Box 92, Folder 2761)
  - Box 47, folder 1334 (Box 92, Folder 2762)
  - Box 47, folder 1339 (Box 92, Folder 2763)
  - Box 47, folder 1348 (Box 92, Folder 2764)
  - Box 48, folder 1360 (Box 92, Folder 2765)
  - Box 48, folder 1361 (Box 92, Folder 2766)
  - Box 48, folder 1369 (Box 92, Folder 2767)
  - Box 48, folder 1370 (Box 92, Folder 2768)
  - Box 48, folder 1371 (Box 92, Folder 2769)
  - Box 48, folder 1373 (Box 92, Folder 2770)
  - Box 48, folder 1377 (Box 92, Folder 2771)
  - Box 48, folder 1381 (Box 92, Folder 2772)
  - Box 48, folder 1383 (Box 92, Folder 2773)
  - Box 49, folder 1393 (Box 92, Folder 2774)
  - Box 49, folder 1394 (Box 92, Folder 2775)
  - Box 49, folder 1398 (Box 92, Folder 2776)
  - Box 49, folder 1408 (Box 92, Folder 2777)
  - Box 49, folder 1409 (Box 92, Folder 2778)
  - Box 49, folder 1413 (Box 92, Folder 2779)
  - Box 49, folder 1417 (Box 92, Folder 2780)
  - Box 49, folder 1423 (Box 92, Folder 2781)
  - Box 49, folder 1424 (Box 92, Folder 2782)
  - Box 49, folder 1425 (Box 92, Folder 2783)
  - Box 50, folder 1427 (Box 92, Folder 2784)
  - Box 50, folder 1438 (Box 93, Folder 2785)
  - Box 50, folder 1439 (Box 93, Folder 2786)
  - Box 50, folder 1444 (Box 93, Folder 2787)
  - Box 50, folder 1451 (Box 93, Folder 2788)
  - Box 50, folder 1453 (Box 93, Folder 2789)
  - Box 50, folder 1455 (Box 93, Folder 2790)
  - Box 50, folder 1462 (Box 93, Folder 2791)
  - Box 50, folder 1463 (Box 93, Folder 2792)
  - Box 50, folder 1465 (Box 93, Folder 2793)
  - Box 51, folder 1469 (Box 93, Folder 2794)
  - Box 51, folder 1473 (Box 93, Folder 2795)
  - Box 51, folder 1474 (Box 93, Folder 2796)
  - Box 51, folder 1482 (Box 93, Folder 2797)
  - Box 51, folder 1484 (Box 93, Folder 2798)
  - Box 52, folder 1493 (Box 93, Folder 2800)
  - Box 52, folder 1494 (Box 93, Folder 2801)
  - Box 57, folder 1513 (Box 93, Folder 2802)
  - Box 57, folder 1514 (Box 93, Folder 2803)
  - Box 58, folder 1568 (Box 93, Folder 2804)
  - Box 58, folder 1575 (Box 93, Folder 2805)
  - Box 58, folder 1576 (Box 93, Folder 2806)
  - Box 58, folder 1578 (Box 93, Folder 2807)
  - Box 58, folder 1579 (Box 93, Folder 2808)
  - Box 58, dolder 1580 (Box 93, Folder 2809)
  - Box 58, folder 1581 (Box 93, Folder 2810)
  - Box 58, folder 1582 (Box 93, Folder 2811)
  - Box 58, folder 1583 (Box 93, Folder 2812)
  - Box 58, dolder 1584 (Box 93, Folder 2813)
  - Box 58, folder 1585 (Box 93, Folder 2814)
  - Box 58, folder 1587 (Box 93, Folder 2815)
  - Box 58, folder 1588 (Box 93, Folder 2816)
  - Box 58, folder 1589 (Box 93, Folder 2817)
  - Box 59, folder 1596 (Box 93, Folder 2818)
  - Box 64, folder 1710 (Box 93, Folder 2819)
  - Box 65, folder 1722 (Box 93, Folder 2820)
  - Box 65, folder 1723 (Box 93, Folder 2821)
  - Box 65, folder 1723 (Box 93, Folder 2822)
  - Box 65, folder 1724 (Box 93, Folder 2823)
  - Box 65, folder 1725 (Box 93, Folder 2824)
  - Box 65, folder 1726 (Box 93, Folder 2825)
  - Box 65, folder 1727 (Box 93, Folder 2826)
  - Box 65, folder 1729 (Box 93, Folder 2827)
  - Box 65, folder 1737 (Box 93, Folder 2828)
  - Box 65, folder 1740 (Box 93, Folder 2829)
  - Box 66, folder 1753 (Box 93, Folder 2830)
  - Box 66, folder 1764 (Box 93, Folder 2831)
  - Box 66, folder 1766 (Box 93, Folder 2832)
  - Box 66, folder 1779 (Box 93, Folder 2833)
  - Box 67, folder 1794 (Box 93, Folder 2834)
  - Box 67, folder 1796 (Box 93, Folder 2835)
  - Box 67, folder 1797 (Box 93, Folder 2836)
  - Box 67, folder 1813 (Box 93, Folder 2837)
  - Box 67, folder 1814 (Box 93, Folder 2938)
  - Box 67, folder 1815 (Box 93, Folder 2839)
  - Box 67, folder 1821 (Box 93, Folder 2840)
  - Box 67, folder 1831 (Box 93, Folder 2841)
  - Box 67, folder 1832 (Box 93, Folder 2842)
  - Box 67, folder 1833 (Box 93, Folder 2843)
  - Box 67, folder 1834 (Box 93, Folder 2844)
  - Box 68, folder 1836 (Box 93, Folder 2845)
  - Box 69, folder 1857 (Box 93, Folder 2846)
  - Box 69, folder 1857 (Box 93, Folder 2847)
  - Box 69, folder 1868 (Box 93, Folder 2848)
  - Box 69, folder 1864 (Box 93, Folder 2849)
  - Box 69, folder 1866 (Box 93, Folder 2850)
  - Box 69, folder 1870 (Box 93, Folder 2851)
  - Box 69, folder 1872 (Box 93, Folder 2852)
  - Box 69, folder 1874 (Box 93, Folder 2853)
  - Box 69, folder 1880 (Box 94, Folder 2854)
  - Box 69, folder 1882 (Box 94, Folder 2855)
  - Box 69, folder 1883 (Box 94, Folder 2856)
  - Box 69, folder 1884 (Box 94, Folder 2857)
  - Box 69, folder 1885 (Box 94, Folder 2858)
  - Box 69, folder 1892 (Box 94, Folder 2859)
  - Box 69, folder 1896 (Box 94, Folder 2860)
  - Box 69, folder 1897 (Box 94, Folder 2861)
  - Box 69, folder 1898 (Box 94, Folder 2862)
  - Box 69, folder 1901 (Box 94, Folder 2863)
  - Box 70, folder 1910 (Box 94, Folder 2864)
  - Box 70, folder 1911 (Box 94, Folder 2865)
  - Box 70, folder 1926 (Box 94, Folder 2866)